早上好  老妈
Good morning, mom.
哦  盖比  亲爱的我们得谈谈
Oh. Gabe, honey. We need to talk.
老妈  不是我的错  是校长跟我过不去
Mom, I didn't do it! That Principal's out to get me.
不是校长的问题
It's not about the Principal.
老妈  不是我的错  是老师跟我过不去
Mom, I didn't do it! That teacher is out to get me.
盖比  你没惹麻烦
Gabe! You're not in trouble.
那么我们要谈什么
Then why do we need to talk?
嗯  是你老爸的事情
Well, it's about your dad.
你也知道他偶尔打呼噜  对吧
Now you're aware that he occasionally snores, right?
哦  老妈  住街那头的人都知道好吗
Mom, the people across the street are aware.
汽车报警器也知道
Car alarms are aware.
整个堪萨斯州都知道吧
Kansas is aware.
好吧  当然  我已经习惯他的呼噜
Well, obviously, I'm used to his snoring
因为老娘在火车轨道边长大的
because I grew up next to train tracks.
但是你老爸总是吵醒托比
But your father's been waking Toby up
我一晚上都要哄宝宝睡觉
and I'm trying to get the baby to sleep through the night.
这一切关我什么事
How does this involve me?
我们打算暂时调整一下就寝安排
We're going to have to temporarily change our sleeping arrangements.
开玩笑吧  你要让我陪托比睡觉
Man, you're putting Toby in with me?
不太准确
Not exactly.
嘿  亲爱的室友
Hey, roomie!
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast</i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>"Has anybody seen my left shoe?"</i>
■
翻译： 寂_翼  Juliet
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： Enpistu
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第十九集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E19  Study Buddy
啊哈
Ah
他终于来了
There he is.
女士们先生们  欢迎维克多·戴力士先生
Mister Victor Deleseur, ladies and gentlemen.
南高中最聪明的人
The smartest guy at South High.
你要我做什么  泰迪
What do you want, Teddy?
什么  难道我总是有目的的吗
What? Do I always have to want something?
难道我不能向对朋友一样邀请你来玩
Can't I just invite you over as a friend to enjoy some...
好吧  其实是这样的
Okay, so here it is.
呃  我这个周末考SAT而且我真的很想考好
Um, I'm taking the SAT this weekend and I really want to ace it.
所以你需要我的帮助因为你知道我拿过2400满分
And you want my help, since you know I scored a perfect 2400.
事实上我还被“成就者月刊”专题报道过
They actually did a feature story on me in "overachievers monthly".
耶  是的  我知道
Yeah yeah, I know.
我还做了剪报贴在本子上呢
I cut it out and put it in my scrapbook.
-真的  -开玩笑的
- Really?!  - No.
所以你觉得呢  会帮我吗
So, what do you say? Will you help me?
有一个条件
Under one condition...
要我给你补习的话
If I tutor you,
我让你做什么你一定要做
you have to agree to do whatever I say no matter what.
没问题
Fine.
现在告诉我你要什么回报
Now just tell me what you want in return.
难道我总是要索取回报吗
Do I always have to want something?
难道我不能只是出于好心
Can't I just do it out of the goodness...
好吧  其实是这样的
Okay, here it is.
我希望你这周六能陪我到公园来
I want you to come to the park with me this Saturday.
等等  你是说像约会那样的
Wait. You mean like a date?
我怎么会邀请你出去
I would never ask you out.
你看  我们都是有主的人了  更重要的是
See, you have a boyfriend, I have a girlfriend and most importantly...
我的择偶标准是对智力要求很高的
I have certain intellectual standards.
挺侮辱人的  不过放心了
Insulted, yet relieved.
那么我们去公园做什么呢
So what are we gonna do at the park?
我有一场很重要的象棋比赛想要你来观战
I have a very important chess match and I'd like you to watch.
- 就这样？  - 就这样
- That's it?  - That's it.
这场比赛肯定另有隐情吧
There's gotta be some sort of catch.
没有图谋  单纯象棋
No catch. Just chess.
这里的象棋是某种代号吗
Is chess a euphemism for something?
就像那种诡异漫画里的角色扮演类的
Like some sort of weird comic book role-playing thing?
当然不是
No.
好吧  没问题
Okay. Fine.
你辅导我  我去公园看你玩怪兽棋
If you tutor me, I'll come to the park and I'll watch you play "chess".
不  不是怪兽棋
No, not "chess".
就是象棋
Just chess.
你是说  捣蛋棋
You mean, "chess".
不  不是捣蛋棋
No! Not "chess".
就是象棋
Just chess!
你将会是我有史以来辅导过得最糟糕的学生了
This may be the toughest tutoring I've ever done.
哦  牛奶甜甜又香香  太好吃了吧
Oh, that is so yummy. Isn't it good?
小查莉  你见过比小托比更可爱的宝宝么
Charlie, have you ever seen a cuter baby in your life?
- 是的  - 是谁
- Yes.  - Who?
我
Me.
有其母必有其女
You are your mother's daughter.
嗨  老妈  小查莉
Hi, mom. Hi, Charlie.
PJ  来帮个忙
PJ, I need your help.
好的老妈  需要我干神马
Sure, mom. What can I do you for?
这是干什么的趣味版说法
It's a fun little way of saying, "what can I do for you?"
忽略掉吧
Proceed.
那个  我现在得去哄托比打个盹
Okay well, I really need to put Toby down for a nap.
但是查莉要人给她念故事书  你能帮忙吗
But Charlie wants me to read to her. can you do it?
当然  没问题  抽点时间来念一本小小故事  哇  这么厚
Oh, yeah. Sure. I got time for a quick little... whoa! Hello.
- 查莉要看这本书  - 或者你来给托比换尿布
- Charlie wants this book? - Would you rather change Toby's diaper?
来吧  小宝贝
Come on, buddy.
小小独角兽
"The Littlest Unicorn".
作者  艾米丽·普拉提布鲁森
"By Emily Prettyblossom".
- 耶  - 好的  第一章
- Yay. - Okay. Chapter one.
许多人说独角兽并不存在于现实中  但是他们是真实的
"Some people say that unicorns aren't real, but they are.
他们来自一个神奇的地方  叫做蝴蝶大陆
They hail from a magical place called Butterflylandia".
哦  天呐
Oh, boy.
接着念嘛
Keep going.
故事就发生在这群独角兽之中  主人公是最小的那一只
"This is the story of one of those unicorns, the littlest one of all".
她叫朱妮  那是她的真名
"Her name was Junie. Her real name, that is".
但是她刻薄的兄弟总是叫她小不点朱妮
"Her mean brothers called her "Junie the Puny Uni".
- 这可不太友好  - 一点都不
- That's not very nice. - No, it isn't.
嘘
Shh.
有一天  朱妮和她的家人去草地上野餐
"One day, Junie and her family went to the meadow for a picnic".
草地紧挨着黑暗森林
"The meadow was right next to the dark forest,
小朱妮被严令禁止进入那里
a place Junie was forbidden to go".
但她的好奇心占了上风
"But her curiosity got the better of her".
- 哦哦  - 我渴了
- Uh-oh. - I'm thirsty.
忍住  朱妮遇到麻烦了
Suck it up. Junie's in trouble.
好  答案是什么
So, what's the answer?
呃
Uh...
- C  - 不不不 是B
- "C"? - No no no, it's "B"!
还蛮接近的
Well, I was close.
泰迪  这是严肃的SAT  不是在玩钉马掌
Teddy, this is the SAT's, not horseshoes!
你知道吗  我们学习了好一会儿了
You know what? We've been going at this for a while.
或许该停下来歇会儿
Maybe we should stop.
停下来  周六就考试了你怎么能停
Stop? But the test is Saturday. You can't stop now.
我们换数学
Let's move on to math.
- 在一个平行四边形里  - 那个  维克多
- In a parallelogram... - Yeah, Victor.
我觉得我学不下去了  我的脑袋已经满了
I don't think I can study anymore. I feel like my brain is full.
那简直太不可思议了  大脑是不会装满的
That's the great thing about brains, they never get full.
即使是像你那么小的
Even smaller ones like yours.
好吧
Okay.
我有必要让你知道真相  我朋友们都觉得我很聪明
I'll have you know, my friends consider me very smart.
你是指艾薇
You mean like Ivy?
嗯  别的朋友也这么看
Well, and other friends.
你是指斯宾塞
You mean like Spencer?
我们还是继续学习吧
Let's get back to work.
当夜幕降临到黑暗森林  朱妮意识到
"And as the sun set on the dark forest, Junie realized she would
她必须独自撑过黑夜
have to survive the night alone".
你害怕吗
Are you scared?
不
No.
我  我也是
Me either.
好了  该睡觉了
Okay, bedtime.
再给我五分钟  看完这章嘛
Five more minutes. We wanna finish this chapter.
抱歉  亲爱的  但是小查莉到睡觉时间了
I'm sorry, honey. But Charlie needs to go to bed.
就是这种父母才会迫使朱妮离开
That's the kind of parenting that drove Junie away
蝴蝶大陆茵茵的绿草地的
from the green pastures of Butterflylandia.
好吧  现在是睡觉时间
Okay. Well, it's bedtime
我可是来自“我不在乎大陆”的
and I'm from the land of "I-don't-care-ia".
快来  查莉
Come on, Charlie.
别担心  我不会背着你往下看的
And don't worry. I won't read ahead without you.
拉钩
Promise?
拉钩  晚安
Promise. Good night.
晚安
Good night.
我都说晚安啦
I said good night.
噢
Oh.
盖比
Gabe.
干嘛  老爸
Yeah, dad?
- 你还没睡  - 睡了 老爸
- You awake? - No, dad.
你想聊天吗
You wanna talk?
不了  老爸
No, dad.
你妈妈总是会让我讲讲我这一天
Your mom usually lets me talk about my day a little.
这样我才能睡好
It helps me fall asleep.
好吧  老爸
Okay, dad.
今天过得怎么样
How was your day?
嗯  今天我去费舍尔太太家了
Well, I was over at Mrs. Fisher's today...
为了工作
Workin'.
得除掉那么多的蜘蛛网
Had to knock down so many spiderwebs.
她最后跟我说
She finally came up to me and she said,
鲍伯  你是不是上周没来
"Bob, did you miss a week?"
我说  不  你这儿就是蜘蛛太多了
I said, "no, you just have a lot of spiders".
晚安吧
Good night.
盖比
Gabe?
老爸  你睡不着的话就看会儿电视吧
Dad, if you can't sleep, just watch some TV.
但是现在是睡觉时间
But it's bedtime.
是吗
Is it?
哇哦  哇哦  哇哦
Whoa! Whoa whoa!
上床后看电视
TV after bedtime?
你常常这么干么
How often you do this?
呃
Um...
这次  嗯  老爸  这次真是第一次
This is, uh... this is my first time, dad.
好  如果弧AB长度为6π
Now, if the semicircle arc "AB" has the length six times PI.
直径为BC的圆周长为8π
And the circumference of the circle with the diameter "BC" is eight times PI...
阴影区域的面积是多少
What is the area of the shaded region?!
呃
Um...
B
"B".
- 错  - 啊哦
- Wrong! - Oh!
你这是干什么
What are you doing?!
为了训练你的大脑进行的惩戒机制
I'm giving you a punishment to train your brain.
维克多  我可不是
Victor, I'm not...
小猫咪
A cat.
嗯  当然不是
Well, of course not.
小猫都能解出那个等式
A cat could have solved that equation.
都半夜了  我们不学了吧
It's midnight. We're done working.
不学了  就因为
We're done? Just because...
都半夜了呢
"It's midnight".
呜呜
sobbing
这确实是我的原话
Yes, that is what I said.
只是没有这损人的语调
Just without the hurtful attitude.
我是来这里浪费时间的吗
Am I wasting my time here?
你真的想这样  我不想你这样
Do you want this?! I don't think you want this!
我不想被这样
I don't want this.
坐下来  打开练习册
Sit down and open that workbook.
就这样  不学了  你被开了
That's it. We're done. You're fired.
- 开除了  - 对
- Fired? - Yup.
解雇了  炒鱿鱼了  恕不远送了
Terminated, dismissed, shown the door.
喔  这是在练习同义词吗
Ooh, we're working with synonyms.
是的  没错  给老娘滚
Yes, we are. Now get out!
走开
Exit!
滚开
Scram!
天呐  看着信息广告
Man, watching infomercials.
牙齿里还夹着爆米花儿
I've got a kernel stuck in my tooth.
没有比这更爽的事情了
Doesn't get any better than this.
嘘 嘘 嘘 嘘
Shh shh shh shh.
有脚步声  关电视
Footsteps! Shut it down!
噢  好吧  到这儿你就不打呼了
Oh, sure. In here you don't snore.
这就来了
There it is.
决战3:10
3:10 to Yuma.
（注：电影名）
太阳出来喜洋洋
Rise and shine.
维克多  我已经把你解雇了
Victor, I fired you.
错了  正确答案是C
Wrong. The correct answer is "C"...
你不能解雇我
I can't be fired.
维克多  现在是早晨六点
Victor. It's 6:00 in the morning.
你究竟来这儿干什么
What in the world are you doing here?
不然我在哪儿
Where else would I be?
天呐  我怎么知道  呆在家
Gee, I don't know. Maybe at home, asleep.
抓着一只科幻公仔睡觉
Clutching some kind of a Sci-Fi action figure.
泰迪  你保证过无论我说什么你都会做
Teddy, you agreed to do whatever I said.
无论什么
No matter what.
欢迎挑战“无论什么”
Welcome to "no matter what"!
你疯了么
Are you crazy?
疯了似地“淆习”
Crazy about learnin'.
这是我第一次也是最后一次把一个字说错
And that's the only time you'll ever hear me drop a "g".
好好听着因为我要说错字了
Listen closely because I'm about to drop a "g".
拱开
"O" away!
好的  好的
This is good. This is good.
你很沮丧  你很生气  你马上就会进入状态了
You're frustrated, you're angry, you're right on schedule.
什么
Excuse me?
每当我帮人家补课的时候这种事情都会发生
This happens whenever I'm working with someone.
他们总在一段时间想放弃
There always comes a moment when they want to quit.
事实上  你崩溃的时间比一般人来得要晚
Actually, your breaking point came later than usual.
这证明你是我最有潜力的学生之一
Which means that you're one of my most promising students.
-是吗   -噢  是的
-Really?  -Oh, yes.
我很佩服你
I am very impressed.
你是颗文曲星啊  泰迪
You're a star, Teddy.
噢  我才不知道什么是文曲星
Oh. I don't know about star.
我的文曲星现在准备好了去学习了么
Is my star ready to get to work now?
得了啦  别说了
Would you stop that?
我去换衣服  马上回来
I'm gonna get dressed. I'll be right back.
文曲星
Star.
-嘿  老妈   -嗨
- Hey, mom.  - Hi.
给我点提示吧
Help me out here.
我是麦瑟瑞德
I'm Mezrab.
再给我点提示
Help me out a little more.
麦瑟瑞德·麦格瑟佩妮  传说中那个半人半兽的巫师
I'm Mezrab Magicpenny, the legendary half-wizard, half-unicorn,
就是朱妮在黑暗森林里遇到的那个
who Junie meets in the dark forest.
我觉得这样能让故事变得更生动
I thought this would help make the story come alive.
为了小查莉吗
For Charlie?
对啊  是的  对啊
Yeah, okay. Yeah.
亲爱的  对不起  查莉还在睡觉呢
Honey, I'm sorry. Charlie's still sleeping.
好吧  要我叫她起床吗
Well, should I wake her up?
好啊  要不我们这样吧
Yeah, you know what?
把托比也叫起床  来办一场派对吧
Let's wake up Toby too. Make it a party.
-好嘞   -不行  给老娘回来
- Okay!  - No! Get back in here!
开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
今天早上你读不了了  查莉要去上幼儿园
You can't read to Charlie this morning. She's got preschool.
噢  好吧  那我至少能吃个早饭吧
Aw, man. Well, can I at least have some breakfast?
好的  来个百吉饼
Sure. Have a bagel.
什么  没有奶油起司
What, no cream cheese?
写不来就不要填
If you don't know then leave it blank.
拿高分得把我谢
When you score high there's me to thank!
让我来把几何料
Geometry is really a breeze.
九十度的是直角
Right triangles are 90 degrees.
齐步走  1  2
Sound off! One, two!
π等于3.14
PI is 3.14.
让我来把歌儿哼
Come on now, let's hear that voice.
多项永远不要蒙
Never guess on multiple choice.
继续再做几道题
Go ahead and do one more!
八八等于六十四
Eight squared is 64!
下次最好把车坐
Next time we should take a car.
我也不想这么弱
I'm not used to running this far.
现在几点啊
What time is it?
凌晨1点
It's 1:00 in the morning.
依旧是我们的故事时间
Also known as story time.
好了  上次读到哪儿了
Okay, where were we?
噢  对了  朱妮在影子洞穴里
Oh, yeah. Junie was at the Cave of Shadows.
“当朱妮走进洞穴的时候  她害怕极了  但同时又非常好奇”
"As Junie entered the cave, she was scared, but also very curious".
“她带着好奇心匍匐前进”
"She crept ahead cautiously".
我好累
I'm tired.
好的  朱妮也很累  但是她依旧坚持前进
Yeah, well, so was Junie. But she keeps going.
打一晚上保龄   老爸  你太强了
All-night bowling... dad, you're an animal!
-PJ   -老爸
- PJ?!  - Dad?
-你要去哪儿   -呃  不去哪儿
- Where are you going? - Uh, nowhere.
-为什么查莉起床了  -不为什么
- Why is Charlie up?  - No reason.
-为什么盖比也起床了  -不为什么
- Why is Gabe up? - No reason.
拿着书干什么
What's with the book?
拿着保龄球干什么
What's with the bowling ball?
什么都没有发生
None of this ever happened.
什么没有发生啊
None of what ever happened?
走吧  老爸  他会问一晚上的
Let's go, dad. He can keep this up all night.
问什么一晚上
Keep what up all night?
“突然  一双绿眼睛突然张开并且岩石洞里升起来”
"Suddenly two bright green eyes opened wide and lit up the rocky den".
"朱妮发现她对面是一个巨大的喷火龙"
"And Junie stood face-to-face with a giant fire-breathing dragon!
“它张大了嘴并且发出一声嘶吼”
"He opened his mouth and roared"...
-PJ  -老妈
-PJ?! -Mom!
你在干嘛呢
What are you doing?
这招只对你爸爸有用
That only works with your dad.
到底怎么回事儿
What's going on here?
这都是查莉的主意   她想要把书看完
It was Charlie's idea. She wanted to finish the book.
噢  好的  所以查莉半夜自己爬起床
Oh, okay. So Charlie got up in the middle of the night,
给你打电话让你从公寓过来把这本书读完
called you at your apartment and told you to come over for a book sesh?
真是个顽皮的小家伙
She's a scamp.
-过来  查莉  -噢  好吧
- Come on, Charlie. - Ah, okay.
晚安  PJ
Good night, PJ.
好吧  她明天要干嘛
Well, what's she doing tomorrow?
-幼儿园  -又上
- Preschool.  - Again?
现在每天都要上了么
That's every day now?
-早上好  盖比   -我不要他住了
- Morning, Gabe.  - I want him out.
-谁  -老爸
- Who?  - Dad.
我已经48小时没有闭过眼了
I haven't slept a wink in 48 hours.
就是今天的数学课上打了一个小盹儿
Except a quick little nap during math class.
是因为他打呼吗
Is this about his snoring?
不是  我只是给他尝了点自由的甜头  然后他就疯了
No! I gave him a taste of freedom and he went crazy.
是的  你爸还是需要规矩的
Yeah. Dad does better with rules.
很多很多的规矩
Lots and lots of rules.
我再也受不了了  你快把他带走  今晚就带走
I can't do it anymore. You gotta take him back. Tonight.
冷静点  好吗
Calm down, okay?
我们在说你爸爸呢
This is your dad we're talking about.
要给点尊重
Let's show a little respect.
我们来抛硬币吧
We'll flip a coin.
-正面朝上  他是你的     -是反面  我来处理
- Heads, you're stuck with him. - Tails, he's my problem.
成交
Deal.
是反面  是反面  是反面
Please be tails. Please be tails. Please be tails.
嘿  干嘛呢你们
Hey. Whatcha doing?
为了你而战斗呢
Fighting over you.
所以谁赢了
So who won?
-噢  盖比   -太棒了
-Aw! Gabe! -Yes!
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
-嗨  -怎么样
- Hi.  - So?
考试怎么样了
How'd the test go?
恩  当然我一时半会儿还不知道成绩  但我觉得发挥得很好
Well.of course I won't know for a while, but I think I did really well.
现在  你要履行和我的契约
Now, in accordance with our agreement,
陪我去参加象棋比赛
you need to accompany me to my chess match.
好  好  象棋比赛
Right right, the "chess match".
-泰迪  它就是个象棋比赛  -当然
- Teddy, it's just a chess match. - Sure.
好吧  那我要穿什么呢
Okay. Well, what do I have to wear? A bird suit or a robot outfit?
其实  你这样穿就很好
Actually, what you have on now is perfect.
快点  安德鲁  该你走了
Come on, Andrew. It's your move.
是吗  哦  好的
It is? Oh, right.
将军
Checkmate.
什么 不  这不可能
What! No! It can't be!
去死吧你  戴力士
Curse you, Deleseur!
我们就此别过吧  谢谢你  泰迪
We're done here. Thank you, Teddy.
让我做书呆子诱饵
Nerd bait.
真是大材小用了
Not my finest hour.
好的  查莉  我已经得到我的SAT成绩了
Well, Charlie. I got my SAT results back,
并且我拿到了一个好成绩
and let's just say I did pretty well.
姐也不想这么目空一切的
I'm trying not to be supercilious.
这个成语我用对了吧
Did I use that right?
爱对不对  都考完了
Who cares? Test's over.
嘿  看看  《小小独角兽》续集已经出来了
Hey, check it out. The sequel to "The Littlest Unicorn" just came out.
《小独角兽的复仇》
"Revenge of The Littlest Unicorn".
看见查莉了吗
Have you seen Charlie?
额  是的  但她让我告诉你她不在家
Uh, yeah. And she told me to tell you that she's not home.
不是吧  那我读给谁听啊
Man! Well, who am I supposed to read this to?
你好  小托比
Hello, Toby!
好的  第一章
Okay, chapter one.
“朱妮有一把斧子要磨”
"Junie had an axe to grind"...
好吧  看来蝴蝶大陆要面临一场疯狂镇压了
Well. Sounds like there's gonna be a beat down in Butterflylandia.
让我们祝朱妮好运吧  小查莉
Better wish Junie some good luck, Charlie.
查莉  准备好去公园了么
Charlie, are you ready to go to the park now?
不要
No!
PJ  因为你那本该死的书查莉已经不敢出去了
PJ, thanks to that stupid book you read her Charlie's afraid to go outside.
她说外面会有一头龙
She thinks there's a dragon out there.
就是有
There is.
你能不能跟你妹妹解释一下
Will you please explain to your sister the
现实和小说的区别
difference between what's real and what's not?
好的  小查莉  很简单
Okay, Charlie. It's very simple.
龙都是假的  独角兽才是真的
Unicorns are real, dragons are not.
好的  现在准备好出门了么
Okay. Are you ready to go now?
不要
No.
老妈  我有办法了  小查莉  外面根本没有龙
Okay, mom. I got this. Charlie, there is no dragon out there.
你要不信就看看我
Look, I'll show you.
早告诉你了
Told you.